You can’t just go and beat a person. For
Нельзя просто взять и побить человека Да
example, at a rally, you can beat
например на митинге вот взять от
him for just standing there with a
дубасить за то что он просто стоит с
white
белым
piece of paper. Hello, I don’t have a flag. I’m
листочком Здравствуйте у меня нет флага
sorry, I’m not sorry. I
Извините не
don’t know why you’re apologizing. Do you feel some kind of
не знаю чувствуешь какую-то
inferiority or that without a flag?
неполноценность свою или что без флага А
No  I fully feel this Well, why did
нет я полноценно се чувству Ну а почему
you suddenly start apologizing that you don’t have a
ты вдруг начал извиняться что у тебя нет
flag, somehow you don’t even have
флага зна как-то показать даже
anything to show and you’re apologizing Why are they
нечего так а извиняешься Почему тебя что
forcing you to show something? No, I
заставляют к что-то показывать Да нет
just wanted to
просто захотелось
apologize, super, you can also Get on your
извиниться супер можете ещё Встать на
knees, a nice apology, not me
колени приятное извинение не я просто
I just think that this is a little little for what Yes
считаю что это мало мало за что Да
Get on your knees then well, to
Встаньте ещё на колени тогда ну чтобы
apologize on
извиниться на
your knees But I don’t don’t want Don’t want Yes, I’m just lying down
коленях А не не хочу Не хотите Да я лёг
already Yes, I could get up like that
просто уже Да так бы так бы может встал
and I could get up I understand what you’re communicating with I’m
а так бы может встать понял а чём
communicating Yes, I don’t know  It’s already boring at night 2
общаюсь Да не знаю Скучно уже ночь 2
nights, I
ночи что-то пообщаться вот
wanted to talk about something, I wanted to talk to the Ukrainians about how they feel about Russia.
захотел с украинцами как они к россие
Why do you need this? Why do you
относятся А зачем вам это Зачем вам
need to know how you feel? Why don’t I need to
знать как вам Зачем так мне не нужно
know how Ukrainians feel about Russia? I
знать как украинцы относятся к России я
don’t go and ask them. Well, you
не хожу и не спрашиваю их Ну ну вы
probably have  you ask Russians No, I don’t ask, I
наверное у русских спрашиваете Нет не
generally think that I think
спрашиваю я вообще считаю что я считаю
that we should not be ordinary Russians
что мы не должны простыми россиянами
because well, you don’t decide anything,
потому что ну вы же ничего не решаете от
nothing depends on you Oh these are very wise
вас ничего не зависит О это очень мудрые
words and I propagate them to everyone in Ukraine
слова и я всем в Украине пропагандируют
Many don’t understand but I say
у меня Многие не понимают но я говорю
So  that Well, nothing depends on them, we
Так что Ну от них ничего не зависит мы
shouldn’t swear at them or have any anger
не должны на них ругаться какую-то злобу
because since the times of Ancient
иметь потому что ещё со времён Древнего
Rome there was a principle that slaves are not
Рима был принцип что рабы не несут
responsible for their master to
ответственность за своего хозяина к
Putin We have serious and
Путину У нас есть претензии серьёзные и
justified claims against you Well, what could they be
обоснованны к вам Ну какие могут быть
This is correct This is not understood by everyone, you
Вот это правильно Это не все понимают да
know why not everyone understands Because
знаете почему не все понимают Потому что
people in Ukraine think in our
люди в Украине они мыслят нашими
categories They think that you are all
категориями Они думают что вы там все
free there too Yes, and you can decide something,
тоже свободные Да и можете что-то решать
something depends on you You can go to
от вас что-то зависит Вы можете там на
rallies there Yes  they don’t understand what
митинги выходить Да они не понимают что
the Territory is there. Well, you’re all Putin’s slaves
там Территория Ну вы все рабы Путина
and you can’t do
типа и не можете ничего сделать
absolutely anything and that’s why they’re angry with you
абсолютно и поэтому на вас злятся потому
because they think that you’re free people. Yeah,
что думают что вы свободные люди
damn, you’re a smart person, very smart. Well, it’s
Угу блин вы умный человек очень умный Ну
good that you’re not like everyone else
хорошо что вы вот не как все остальные в
sitting here in helmets  with the flags behind them they
касках тут сидят с флагами сзади
swear or send you to hell So wait,
ругаются или нахуй посылают Так подожди
look They swear because they have
смотри Они ругаются потому что э они ещё
n’t yet reached that level of knowledge that
не дошли до того уровня познания что вот
your country is not free and you are not
у вас несвободная страна и вы не
free people That is, if they
свободные люди То есть если бы они это
understood this, they wouldn’t have any complaints against
понимали да у них бы не было претензий к
you  would be a complaint against your
вам был бы претензии к вашему
slave owners, yes, that is, we have them
рабовладельцы да то есть у нас они
thinking. Why do they? Well, people
мыслят Почему они Ну люди никогда не
have never been to Russia and they don’t see what’s
были в России и они не видят что у вас
going on there. They think that you have the
там происходит Они думают что у вас
same democracy as we have here, rallies,
также как у нас тут демократия митинги
damn it. By the way, I don’t even  I knew about
там блин Я кстати даже не знал про
rallies in
митинги в
Ukraine, you were often held there before the
Украине вас там частенько устраивали до
war, and even now there are even rallies going on
войны Да и сейчас даже проходят митинги
now. And now that they also have
и сейчас А сейчас-то что уних тоже там
someone there. They want something there; there are drones instead of
кто-то Хочет там что-то там дроны вместо
brukivkas; someone else wants something else.
там брукивки кто-то ещё что-то хочет
Even  now, during martial
Даже даже сейчас во время ээ военного
law, when mass
положения ходя когда ограничены массовые
gatherings are limited, people still hold it and
собрания всё равно даже люди проводят и
no one disperses them, no one
никто их не разгоняет не
beats them. Damn, we would have killed everyone. Well,
бьёт Блин у нас бы поса зали всех
look, I’ll say. So now
Да ну смотрите я скажу Так что сейчас
it’s going along with other democratic
идёт вместе с другими демократическими
countries, there’s
странами есть вот
this front like that, yeah  The world is against
этот фронт такой да Мировой против вот
this dictatorship, sooner or later you
этой диктатуры рано или поздно вас
will be released, of course, it is better for you that
освободят конечно для вас лучше чтобы
it is early and not late because, well,
это было рано А не поздно потому что ну
many of you tolerate this regime. Yes,
многие из вас терпят этот режим Да
many are aware of their such position and
многие осознают там свою такую позицию и
help somehow shake this regime
помогают как-то шатать этот режим
because even if, for example  there was a slave in the
потому что даже если например вот раб на
gallery Yes, once upon a time in ancient times
галери был Да когда-то вот в древности
Yes he They could have made an uprising They could
Да он Они могли сделать Восстание Могли
have made it so that a riot in the gallery could have been
сделать так чтобы бунт на галере могли
broken Oars could have been done, in short,
там ломать Вёсла могли короче делать
all sorts of nasty things Yes in order to cause damage to the
всякие гадости Да чтобы урон наносить
slave
рабо
owner then what happened like in Pakistan
владельцу потом что было как в Пакистане
or where there was a
или где
coup
переворот
state I mean,
государственный В
well, as if why is it necessary? I’m
смысле Ну как будто зачем она надо я вот
living a routine house work house me
Живу рутинного дом работа дом меня вот
this coup is actually not very much
этот переворот на самом деле не очень то
no it’s not a coup look
нет это же не есть переворот смотрите
the coup was already a coup just
переворот уже был переворот как раз
when they seized power from you Yes and
когда у вас захватили власть Да и
it turns out they made you slaves  That was a
получается сделали вас рабами Вот это
revolution, yes yes Well, I
был переворот да да Ну я себя рабом
somehow feel like a slave And I don’t feel, you know, you don’t feel Yes,
как-то И не ощущаю знаете не ощущаешь Да
maybe you don’t feel it, yes Well, look, the fact is
может не ощущаешь да Ну смотри Дело в
that a person who is a slave does not
том что человек который есть рабом он не
always feel like a slave, for example, a
всегда себя ощущает рабом например
person who lives in poverty. But a homeless person, for
человек который живёт бедности Да вот
example, a homeless person  he doesn’t feel like a
бомж например бомж он себя не ощущает
homeless person, he feels like a
бомжом он себя ощущает например
free person, for example. Yes, but for society
свободным человеком Да но для общества
he is like a homeless person. Yes, he
типа он есть как бы бомжом Да у него
doesn’t have any rights and so on. Well,
нету каких-то там прав и так дальше Ну
property, that is, the question is not how you
имущества то есть Вопрос не в том как вы
feel about yourself. You can feel
себя ощущаете Вы можете себя ощущать
like  what do you have there, in short, you're a cool
типа что у вас там короче вы классный
jock Like the girls like you
качок Типа вы нравитесь девушкам у вас
In short, everything is like this and the girls look at it
Короче всё так а девушки на это смотрят
differently the truth is that the question is
по-другому правда вот то есть вопрос не
not how you feel, yes And who you really are Well,
то как вы себя ощущаете да А кем вы есть
even if in comparison  anyway,
Ну даже если в сравнении то всё равно
somehow
как-то
everything looks good Well, that is,
неплохо всё выглядит Ну то есть паёк
they give rations there, as if you know, among the slaves, it was also like that
дают там как бы знае у рабов тоже так
there in the morning at lunch and in the evening
было там утром в обед и вечером
they fed Yes, they gave some Well, it’s
накормили Да дали какую-то Ну и
normal to eat, it doesn’t rain,
нормально есть дождь не капает
like eat, yes, they
типа кушать да
don’t beat you too hard, like you know  Well, there
да сильно не бьют типа знаешь Там ну
are
есть
rules there, stick to them, and then they don’t
правила придерживайся их да тогда не
beat you up, so it’s
лупят так что
normal. We also
нормально У нас так же
probably don’t have anything against this government,
наверно ничего против этот правительства
which means
не имеешь значит
you live normally, this is when they already
нормально живёшь это когда уже
threw little into the bowl. Yes,
там мало в миску кидали Да
we don’t finish eating. Yes, for example,
уже не доедаем Да например
or when they’re already beating them hard, like,
или когда уже сильно типа лупят типа
although not  Usually when they hit me hard And from
Хотя не Обычно когда сильно лупили А с
hunger I still rebelled Yes, the fish got hit hard, no, I
голоду ещ бунтова Да рыбы сильно луп не
don’t remember this Yes in
не бунтова не помню такого Да в
history It’s
истории
clear Damn, they directly loaded themselves with work,
Понятно Блин прямо загрузили рабо себя
you felt like it was happening Well, you see, it’s like, well,
почувствовал дело Ну видишь ты как бы ну
you’re de facto a person without rights Yes,
ты дефакто есть человек без прав Да
you just felt like you’re what  - it turns out that
просто ты себя ощущал что ты что-то вот
the citizen turns out to be Yes, we need to
гражданин оказывается Да надо по-другому
look at it differently But I will say this thing is
Взглянуть на это Но я скажу такое дело в
that after the de-occupation of the Russian
том что после деоккупации Российской
Federation Yes, after the
Федерации Да после Свер Вот это
Great Patriotic regime that captured
тического режима который захватил
all the Russians, Russians, and so on Yes, they
россиян русских всех и так дальше Да
will be done under the leadership of the UN, here I am
будут сделаны под руководством ООН вот я
now entering  also in some working
сейчас вхожу тоже в некоторые рабочие
groups on the division of the Russian
группы по разделению Российской
Federation, the introduction of external control
Федерации введение внешнего управления
so that there is no chaos at the moment, well,
для того чтобы не было хаоса в момент ну
because after all, it’s a big country. So
потому что всё-таки большая страна Так у
you have all sorts of Armed groups there
вас там всякие куча Вооружённых групп
now after s Yes, so that they immediately take
сейчас после с Да чтобы сразу взяли под
control, for example, there will be a zone of
контроль например будет зона
responsibility, for example  there the USA France
ответственности например там США Франции
Great Britain China Japan uh for
Великобритании Китая Японии ээ для для
control under the UN mandate so that there
контроля под мандатом ООН чтобы не было
is no police
будут полицейские
functions to be performed so that there are no
функции исполнять чтобы не было каких-то
pogroms and robberies there for the first
Там погромов грабежей первые типа
six months So it will be necessary to establish uh a
полгода Так нужно будет наладить ээ
new local government,
новое местное самоуправление будут
instructors will come who will
приезжать инструктора которые будут
teach, but it will take a long time  within 10 years it
учить но это долго будет лет 10 надо
will be necessary to carry out democratic
будет проводить демократические
procedures. Yes, for example, I’ll be
процедуры Да например вот я буду
coming. Well, I don’t know, that’s
приезжать Ну в Новосибирск не знаю это
not true. It’s cool, yes, for example, I’ll
не Прикольно да я например там в
come there to Krasnodar; I have a
Краснодар приеду у меня там блогеров
lot of acquaintances of these bloggers there. It’s cool, yes, yes, there are
этих много знакомых Прикольно да да там
a lot of these Russian bloggers, yes,
блогеров много знакомых этих российских
we’ll tell them the reception  that
Да мы им приём будем рассказывать то
is, democratic procedures How to
есть демократические процедуры Как из
become a free person from a slave,
рабом из раба стать свободным человеком
yes, that is, What is the difference between a slave and a
да то есть В чём отличие раба и
free person, what does a free
свободного человека что вот свободный
person influence depends on him? He is a
человек влияет от него зависит Он
citizen, he has rights, some
гражданин у него есть права какие-то
rights to elect and the right to disagree there.
права избирать да права там не
For example, if the government does
соглашаться Например если власть делает
something that does not contradict the Constitution,
что-то что не противоречит Конституции
that is, basic rights and freedoms, that you
да то есть базовым правам и свободам что
can’t just go and beat a person.
нельзя просто взять и побить человека Да
Yes, for example, at a rally, you can take
например на митинге вот взять от
a beating for simply standing with a
дубасить за то что он просто стоит с
white piece of paper, that is, they will teach,
белым листочком да то есть будут учить
at first there will be rejection, and many
сначала будет отторжение да у многих
because  that Well, to understand and how it
потому что Ну поняти и как для людей вот
will be scary for people to understand how so that you can
страшно будет понять как так что можно
go out and hold a rally. Yes, how can you
выходить и митинг Да как можно это вот
go out to the square and say something to the authorities?
на площадь выйти и что-то сказать власти
Because there is this
Потому что есть вот эта такая
sacredness of power that it is there that the Tsar
сакральность власти что это там царь
Emperor will teach, we will give,
император будем учить будем приводить
for example  we’ll take groups Yes, for example,
например будем брать группы Да например
look at the grandmothers or we’ll
так вот смотрите бабушки или там эти
bring these to rallies so shout, yes, for example,
приведём на митинги так крикните да
they will be shy there at first
например они там сначала будут
Well, shout out what
стесняться Ну вот крикните что у вас
hurts you, for example, and they’ll shout there like
болит например и они там крикну там типа
we want a pension Yes And there will be such a thing, you know,
хотим пенсии Да И вот будет такое знае
retraining, as it were  the entire
пере как бы переобучение целого
population of the former country Yes, the former
населения бывшей страны Да бывшей
Russian
Российской
Federation May I
Федерации Дай бов
understand
понял
sadly all this Well, you need to retrain It’s
грустно всё это Ну надо переучивать
hard, yes, teach, look, well, as they say,
Тяжело да учи смотри ну как говорят
teaching is light and not teaching is darkness, cosma
учение свет а не учение тьма козма
Prutkov said Yes,
Прутков говорил Ещё
and everyone needs to learn, yes they will Many will
да и всё надо учиться да будут Многие
want to remain ignorant, say don’t
захотят остаться неучем сказат не
let us not  we want these elections Give
давайте мы не хотим вот эти выборы Дайте
us some kind of new owner Yes and let
нам какой-то нового хозяина Да и пусть
it be like it doesn’t matter even America
будет типа уже пофиг хоть Америка
No how many years has Captain been at the helm
ть Сколь сколько лет уже у руля Капитан
Everyone has already gotten used to it and the older generation
Все уже привыкли так и старшее поколение
and our generation now are just
и наше сейчас поколение просто просто
like Many were even born on this
уже типа Многие даже родились на этой
galley it turns out  that is, they are many Yes
галере получается то есть они многие Да
Many don’t even know freely there is an even
Многие даже не знают свободно есть ещё
older generation They at least grabbed a zero there
старшее поколение Они хоть хват нули там
for a couple of years after the collapse of the Soviet
уже пару лет после развала Советского
Union of some breath of Freedom Yes and
Союза какого-то глотка Свободы Да а
then
потом
like that’s all And many have already been born and
типа и всё А много уже родилась и
raised and have not seen anyone except
выросла и никого не видела кроме как
this
этой
life
жизни
Yes, I don’t even know how it will be in
Да даже не знаю как это потом будет в
the future, many people I asked
будущем многие вот у кого спрашивал даже
don’t even know what will happen after
не знают что вот будет после того как
Putin leaves. And what awaits Russia, it’s
Путин уйдёт А что вот Россию ждёт она
the same as the USSR, probably absolutely
тоже же как СССР наверное абсолютно раз
because Look, the thing is that
потому что Смотрите дело в том что
Russia is a geopolitical  subject, it has
Россия как геополитический субъект она
outlived its usefulness, it should have
себя изжила она должна должна была ещё
collapsed in 1917, that’s how the
развалиться в 1917 году вот как
Russian Empire collapsed
Российская империя развалилась потому
because all empires collapsed at the beginning of the
что все империи разваливались в начале
20th century, Austria, Hungary collapsed and
XX века Австрия Венгерская развалилась и
live normally separately, Austria
живут нормально отдельно Австрия
separately, Hungary separately, Slovakia, Czech Republic
отдельно Венгрия отдельно Словакия Чехия
now, yes, that is, yes, the Russian
сейчас да то есть да вот Российская
Empire also collapsed  there Finland
империя также развалилась там Финляндия
Poland Ukraine Bashkartastan a lot of everything
Польша Украина башкартастан куча всего
yes Lenin reassembled a little like part of the
да Ленин пересобрал немножко типа часть
territories Yes he collected and made the Soviet
территорий Да собрал и сделал Советский
Union Yes the Soviet Union is still
Союз Да Советский Союз всё равно это
completely different cultures there, peoples are
абсолютно разные там культуры народы
absolutely incompatible Yes they fell apart with each other
абсолю несовместимые Да друг с другом
In the ninety-first year from
развалился В девяносто первом году от
these contradictions Yes this was the second stage
этих противоречий Да это был второй этап
collapse of the Russian Empire
распада Российской Империи
Yes, the third stage of the collapse of the Russian
Да третий этап распада Российской
Empire - this will be the final
Империи - это будет уже окончательный
collapse of the Russian Federation into
развал Российской Федерации на
national states there Tatarstan
национальные государства там Татарстан
Bashkartastan Chechnya And so on and
башкартастан Чечня И так дальше и
regional ones, for example Novosibirsk It’s
региональные так да например Новосибирск
okay that, for example, But in
Ничего страшного что например Бут там в
Siberia there is their own state, for example
Сибири своё государство например
Russian-speaking, but if we take
русскоязычное вот если мы возьмём
Spanish-speaking  there is Spain, it once
испаноязычные есть Испания она когда-то
held colonies there in Latin America
держала колонии там в Латинской Америке
in South America Yes, now in Mexico they
в Южной Америке Да сейчас в Мексике
speak Spanish, but this is another country that
говорят по-испански но это другая страна
has nothing to do with Spain Cuba
к Испании ничего не имеет Куба
in Spanish Yes, all of South America except
по-испански Да вся Южная Америка кроме
Brazil something else there Yes  He
Бразилии что-то там чего ещё одного Да
also speaks everything in Spanish, and all the
тоже по-испански всё говорит да и все
countries are different, and nothing prevents them from living
разные страны и ничего им не мешает жить
separately, yes And building their politics
отдельно да И строить свою политику
separately, yes, that is, St. Petersburg, it
отдельно да то есть санкт-петербург это
will be a free Ingria, you will
будет свободная ингрия у вас там будет
know how the republic is, it doesn’t matter, yes, that is,
знаю как республика неважно да то есть
what you will call Seya  that is, in the
как вы Сея будете называть то есть в
Far East it’s different. Well, you and the
Дальнем Востоке другое это ж Вот вы и
Far East are completely different
Дальний Восток это совсем разные как
worlds and Moscow and these are different worlds Well,
миры и Москва и это разные миры Ну
yes, yes,
да
of course it’s time to divide It seems to me Well,
да да конечно пора делить Мне кажется Ну
how can it be, I don’t know who except Putin,
как может вот не знаю кто кроме Путина
then well, the next one will come there, I don’t know
потом ну следующий придёт там не знаю
who  maybe it’s possible to keep an eye
кто может
on a huge country? Yes, well, they don’t
при огромной страной следить Да ну не
keep track; the point is not even to keep track; not to
следят за суть не в том даже следить не
keep track; the point is that this country is
следить Суть в том что эта страна
artificial; yes, this is a country like a remnant of the
искусственная Да это страна как остаток
Russian Empire with completely different
Российской империи с абсолютно разных
cultures; Islam is there;
культур там Ислам там
Christianity is there; Buddhism is there; and so on; yes,
э христианство там буддизм И так дальше
completely different.
Да абсолютно разных исторических
ethnic historical regions, yes, that is, such a
регионов этнических да то есть такая
mess
каша
is simply supported by bayonets, like
э держится просто просто на штыках типа
before the Putin regime, and that’s all if you leave
до путинского режима и всё если оставить
it. Yes, it will be the same, the same
её Да будет то же самое та же самая
imperial policy will be and that’s all, that’s why
имперская политика будет и всё поэтому
it’s natural, that it will fall apart, okay, I’ll
она природная что она развалится хорошо
run further, let’s, let
всё побегу дальше давайте давайте
’s
давайте
for now  This is
пока Вот
how we must convey to the Russians
так мы должны доносить к россиянам
Yes, what is the situation
Да что в каком положении
they are in and what is the way out of this
они находятся и какой выход из этого
situation, the way out of this situation Yes, the
положения выход из этого положения Да
collapse of the Russian Federation, replacing the
развал Российской Федерации замена
President of the Tsar will not solve anything, but it’s
президента царя этого ничего не решит Да
as if he will replace one Tsar with
что как бы вместо одного царя поставит
another Who is the Heir there, conditionally yes
другого Кто там Наследник там условно да
and all the writing on y Telegram right now axis
и всё пись на й Telegram прям зараз ось
VN
ВН
apok tse more and more respectfully YouTube keeping
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us busy through skarg Orcs in your ban and even
нас через скарг Орки в твый бан и дуже
more videos I don’t show people at the moment I don’t
багато видео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about ST for this purpose
показуе информация про СТ тому для того
for Mali operational link to write
щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок пишиться
directly at once  while there in telegra okm vdeo
прямо зараз а пок там в телегра окм вдео
shche tezh tsikava and korisna information and mi
ще теж цикава и корисна информация и ми
povinni z you trimati postiyny
повинни з вами тримати
operational link
постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava Ukra pis
YouTube Слава Укра
Ne
Ne